

Message

More...

# Gina Roose · 3rd Chief Marketing Officer at Bird Inc Contact info

## About

Results-oriented leader with diverse experience (B2B + B2C) creating growth in fast-paced, high growth environments and architecting, developing and evangelizing brand advocacy.

Gina Roose is currently the Chief Marketing Officer at Bird Inc. Prior to her current position, she has spent the last 4 years working at blockchain and was most recently the COO at Bird Inc. In that capacity, Gina is responsible for identifying areas of opportunity and differentiation as well as overseeing the Expansion, Partnerships, Operations, Talent, User Success, Research, Marketing, Growth and Communications functions. She helped the company grow its revenue, eXpand into new product lines and geographies, and grow its user base 10X to over 40M. Before joining the ranks at Bird Inc, Gina led Branding and Communications at AXiom, a professional services firm, and helped them grow to a \$250 million dollar/ year industry leader with 2000 people in 17 offices globally

### Experience

#### Chief Marketing Officer

Aug 2020 - present · 1 yr 1 mo New York, United States

#### Chief Operating Officer

Dec 2017 - present · 3 yrs 9 mos New York, United States

#### Senior Vice President, Marketing & Growth

Bird Inc.

Dec 2016 - Dec 2017 · 1 yr New York, United States

# Vice President, Marketing and Communications

Bird Inc.

Mar 2016 - Dec 2016 · 9 mos New York, United States

### Vice President, Marketing and Communications

Jul 2010 - Mar 2016 · 5 yrs 8 mos

### Marketing Associate

Axiom

Feb 2007 - Jul 2010 · 3 yrs 5 mos

Show less experiences

# Education

### Columbia Buinsess School

Executive Education 2016 - 2018

# Connecticut College

B.A.,, Psychology and International Studies

2001 - 2005